Guide to the Thomas Rain Crowe Papers, 1965-2020 RL.10018
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Addition (2019-0178), 1994-2019
  - Writings, 2001-2019
    - Yvonn Goll miscellaneous translations, 2012-2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 1)
    - The Inner Trees, Selected Poems by Yvonn Goll book, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 1)
    - Mountain Places: A Poetry and Prose Anthology, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Starting from San Francisco: Thomas Rain Crowe in Conversation with Third Mind Books (book), 2018 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Starting from San Francisco interview with NPR on the State of Things, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Hendershot, Don, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Gates and Towers draft, 2001 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
  - Writings by Others, 2018-2019
    - Bledsoe, Linda, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Book editing job for Lisa Ezzard, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Martin, Brent, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Napora, Joe, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Olson, Mary (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Revere, Michael (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Editing Job for Michael Revere, 2018-2019; 2 folders (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Stark, Jessica (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Editing job for Dee Stribling (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
    - Warren, Ken, 2019 (Box Acc. 19/178: Box 2)
- Addition (2020-0069)
  Access note. Collection contains electronic records that may need to be reformatted. Access copies of electronic records must be accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services for access.
  Access restricted; collection requires additional arrangement, description, and/or screening. Contact research services for more information.
  Accession 2020-0069 is unprocessed; it includes correspondence, manuscript drafts, unprocessed electronic media, and personal and professional files related to Crowe's writing, editing, publishing, and activism.
  - Box 1 (Box Acc.20/0069: Box 1)
  - Box 2 (Box Acc.20/0069: Box 2)
  - Box 3 (Box Acc.20/0069: Box 3)